

Xavier Hernandez-Martinez

Web Developer

(+33) 6 26 09 19 66 xhernan.martinez@gmail.com www.xhernandez.me linkedin.com/in/xavihrez github.com/XavHernandez

Profile

In professional retraining after a 10-year career as LiveOps manager for the french iGaming market leader. Graduated from Le Wagon bootcamp and self-taught, I am now looking for a developer position (Vue / Nuxt / Ruby on Rails). Professional and hardworking, I also offer real added value to my technical skills through solid experience in product management.

Skills

{
JavaScript,
Vue / Nuxt,
Ruby,
Ruby on Rails,
HTML5 / CSS3,
Bootstrap,
Sass,
SQLite,
PostgreSQL,
Git / Github,
Heroku,
}

Experience

LIVE OPERATIONS MANAGER

WINAMAX | PARIS, FR | JUL 2010 - SEPT 2019

- Orchestrated launch for products and promotions with development and creative teams.
- Managed product backlog/roadmap to optimize game client and products.
- Collaborated with development teams to optimize back-office tools.
- Designed, deployed and managed full online gaming offers (schedule and money flow).

ONLINE MARKETING EXECUTIVE

WINAMAX | LONDON, UK | AUG 2009 - JUN 2010

- Coordinated with B2B providers and customer support to manage gaming
- Created and maintained online content materials for products, promotions and game client.
- Deployed and managed gaming offers for french online communities.

Education

Le Wagon Bordeaux - Full Stack Web Development CODING BOOTCAMP Q2 - 2021

Kagilum / Wensei - Professional SCRUM Certification September 2020

Universite Bordeaux III - Information & Communication DUT Information & Communication Sustainable Development Option 2007 - 2008